Inventory of the William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation records
Hoover Institution Archives
William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation records
1918-2002
1980-2002
2002C69
Hoover Institution Archives
51 manuscript boxes, memorabilia (21.3 linear feet)
Minutes, meeting materials, correspondence, financial records, printed matter, and memorabilia relating to efforts to promote the legacy of the United States Office of Strategic Services.
William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2002.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
The William J. Donovan Foundation, a private American nonprofit organization, was created in the early 1980s with the goal of promoting the life and legacy of Donovan, the head of the Office of Strategic Services (OSS), the American intelligence agency active during World War II. The Foundation’s membership and Board of Directors met annually.
The Foundation awarded a William J. Donovan Medal to notable persons who were seen to embody the values of Donovan. It also sought to establish a fellowship in Donovan’s name that would be given to students in foreign affairs. The Foundation ceased operations in the late 1990s.
Scope and Content of Collection
The William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation records contain minutes of meetings, reports, and financial records that detail the work of the organization. The mainstay of the group was Geoffrey Jones, whose extensive correspondence with members and others is a major part of the records.
United States. Office of Strategic Services.; Secret service--United States.; World War, 1939-1945--Secret service.; Donovan, William J. (William Joseph), 1883-1959.
- Correspondence and clippings relating to the United Nations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1: 1-4)
- Betac Corporation correspondence and reports, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 5)
- Background materials for history of foundation, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 1: 6)
- Mailing announcing closure of foundation, 2002 (Box-folder 1: 7)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1: 8-9)
- Correspondence relating to closure of foundation, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1: 10)
- Chase Manhattan correspondence and forms, 2001 (Box-folder 1: 11)
- Directors' communications, 2001 (Box-folder 1: 12)
- Register of members' addresses, 2001 (Box-folder 1: 13)
- Letter to contributors, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 1-5)
- List of contributors, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 6-7)
- List of contributions to office fund, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 8)
- Financial statement mailing, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 9)
- Membership booklet mailing, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 10)
- Membership mailing, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 11)
- Rent/overhead contributors, undated (Box-folder 2: 12-13)
- Acknowledgment letter, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 14)
- Acknowledgment cards, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 15)
- Certificate of incorporation, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 16)
- Explanatory statement, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 17)
- Letterheads, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 3: 1-2)
- Return envelopes, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 3)
- Fax sheet, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 4)
- Change of address form, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 5)
- Philip Schaff correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 6)
- List of contributions, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 3: 7)
- Jedburgh reunion donations, 1987 (Box-folder 3: 8)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1982-1994 (Box-folder 3: 9)
- Notes and draft of letter, 1998 (Box-folder 3: 10)
- Correspondence relating to office fund appeal, 1998 (Box-folder 3: 11)
- Donation envelopes sent by contributors, 1998 (Box-folder 3: 12)
- Lease for office, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 4: 1)
- Correspondence with George H. W. Bush, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 4: 2-6)
- Donovan Fellowships in Foreign Affairs proposal, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 4: 7)
- A. B. Krongard correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 4: 8-9)
- National Security Fellowship proposal, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 10)
- Aide-mémoire, 2001 (Box-folder 4: 11)
- Office insurance policy, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 4: 12-13)
- Lease cancellation, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 14)
- Agenda and minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1999 May 25 (Box-folder 5: 1-4)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes related materials.
- Minutes of meetings and related correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5: 5-7)
- Geoffrey Jones mailing, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 8)
- Notice about annual meeting, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 9)
- Agenda, proxies, and reports for annual meeting, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 10-13)
- Executive Committee meeting correspondence and notes, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 14)
- Minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5: 15)
- Advisory Council mailing, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 16)
- Geoffrey Jones's correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 17)
- Financial report, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 18)
- Background materials, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5: 19)
- Current file, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5: 20)
- Correspondence relating to Board of Directors, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 21)
- Proxies for Board of Directors meeting, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 22)
- Mailing relating to Board of Directors, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 23)
- Treasurer's report, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 24)
- Mailing, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 25)
- Correspondence relating to Executive Committee meeting, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 26)
- Finances and lease, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 1)
- Chronological files, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 6: 2-5)
- Aide-mémoire, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 6)
- Frank G. Wisner correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 7)
- Minutes of special Board of Directors meeting, 1998 October 14 (Box-folder 6: 8)
- Special Board of Directors meeting correspondence and notes, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 9)
- General correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 10)
- Annual meeting agenda, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 11)
- Notice of annual meeting, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 12)
- Board of Directors meeting agenda and financial report, 1998 December 1 (Box-folder 6: 13)
- Agenda and financial reports for annual meeting, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 14)
- Center for Security Policy programs and reports, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 7: 1-4)
- Kevin Burke correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 5-6)
- Final versions of notices and reports, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 7-8)
- Miscellaneous clippings, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 9)
- Certificates and membership solicitation materials, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 10)
- Invitations, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 11)
- Master copies of invitation and primer, 1983-1999 (Box-folder 7: 12)
- Contributor correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 7: 13)
- Green Mountain Graphics correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 14)
- Microfilm reels, 1950 (Box-folder 8: 1-9)
- Annual meeting reports and proxies, 1996 November 20 (Box-folder 9: 1)
- Lists of contributors and update letter, 1996 (Box-folder 9: 2)
- Minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1996 November 26 (Box-folder 9: 3-4)
- Notice of annual meeting, 1996 (Box-folder 9: 5)
- Donor's list and proxy for annual meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 9: 6)
- Agenda for Board of Directors meeting, 1997 December 4 (Box-folder 9: 7)
- Notice of annual meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 9: 8)
- Minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 9: 9)
- Leona Forman correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 10)
- Brochures, newsletter, and report relating to the United Nations; announcement of fellowship program, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9: 11)
- Philanthropy magazine article and correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 12)
- Stephen Ambrose correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 13)
- Clippings and notes relating to Steven Spielberg, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 14)
- Donovan Fellowships announcement, 1997 (Box-folder 9: 15)
- Kenneth Rendell correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 9: 16-17)
- Letter to Steven Spielberg, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 18)
- Statement on William J. Casey, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 19)
- Mrs. William J. Casey correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 9: 20)
- Special Board of Directors meeting proxies and notes, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 1)
- Notice of special Board of Directors meeting, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 2)
- Financial reports, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 3)
- Agenda and minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 4-5)
- Notes, proxies, and minutes relating to Board of Directors meeting, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 10: 6)
- List of donations, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 7)
- Martin S. Quigley correspondence and financial records, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 8)
- Correspondence and proxies relating to Board of Directors meeting, 1994 November 15 (Box-folder 10: 9)
- Notice and agenda of annual meeting, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 10)
- Director's letters and financial records, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 11)
- Working materials for Board of Directors meeting, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 12)
- Donovan Fellowships Program letter, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 13)
- Letter and minutes of Board of Directors meeting, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 14)
- William E. Colby letter and financial records, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 15)
- Agenda for annual meeting, 1995 November 21 (Box-folder 10: 16)
- Board of Directors meeting reports, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 17)
- Financial records, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 18)
- Notice of annual meeting, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 19)
- Letter to advisory council members and donor list, 1996 (Box-folder 10: 20)
- Charter/donor update letter, 1996 (Box-folder 10: 21)
- Agenda of Board of Directors meeting, 1996 November 26 (Box-folder 10: 22)
- 4 framed copies of portrait of William J. Donovan, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 1-4)
- Financial records, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 12: 1)
- Donor correspondence and minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1990 (Box-folder 12: 2)
- New Directors correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 12: 3)
- Correspondence, reports, and notes relating to Board of Directors meeting, 1990 (Box-folder 12: 4)
- Notice of annual meeting and financial records, 1990 (Box-folder 12: 5)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1991 (Box-folder 12: 6)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors and financial records, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 12: 7)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and financial records (Box-folder 12: 8)
- Financial records, 1991 (Box-folder 12: 9)
- Agenda and financial records for Board of Directors meeting, 1991 (Box-folder 12: 10)
- Agenda and financial report for Board of Directors meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 11)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1992 October 27 (Box-folder 12: 12)
- Financial report and agenda for Board of Directors meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 13)
- Announcement of Donovan Fellowships, 1999 (Box-folder 12: 14)
- Agenda and correspondence relating to Board of Directors meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 15)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 16)
- Financial records, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 13: 1-5)
- Tax returns and financial statement, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 13: 6)
- Mario Machado correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 14: 1)
- Kay Sugahara correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 14: 2)
- Cristina Ventry correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 14: 3)
- Articles, correspondence, and memoranda relating to potential donors, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 14: 4-9)
- Donor list, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15: 1)
- Proposal for development grant, 1999 (Box-folder 15: 2)
- Budget, 1998 (Box-folder 15: 3)
- Finance-related correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 4)
- Appeal to donors, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 5)
- Office ledgers, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 15: 6)
- Printed matter relating to the United Nations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 15: 7)
- Correspondence and reports, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 15: 8)
- David R. Bruce correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Walter J. P. Curley correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 16: 2)
- Michel de Bourbon de Parme correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 16: 3)
- John J. Devine correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 16: 4)
- John R. Drexel IV correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 16: 5)
- Addresses of Board of Directors, 1999 (Box-folder 16: 6)
- Donovan/OSS symposium correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 16: 7)
- Correspondence to and from Directors, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 16: 8)
- Memoranda to Directors, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 16: 9)
- Funding correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 16: 10)
- Notes written by Geoffrey Jones, 1982 (Box-folder 16: 11)
- List of Directors, 1993 (Box-folder 16: 12)
- Working file, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 16: 13)
- Tax returns, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 16: 14)
- Financial records and related correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 16: 15-16)
- Donor lists, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 16: 17)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 16: 18)
- Operating budgets, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 16: 19)
- Correspondence relating to If Donovan Were Here Today booklet, 1988 (Box-folder 17: 1)
- Letter from John E. Tobin, 1985 (Box-folder 17: 2)
- William J. vanden Heuvel correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 17: 3)
- Appeal to donors, undated (Box-folder 17: 4)
- James R. Withrow, Jr. correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 17: 5)
- Evangeline Bruce correpondence, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 6)
- William J. Casey correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 17: 7)
- William E. Colby correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 17: 8)
- Henry B. Hyde correspondence and clippings, 1983-1997 (Box-folder 17: 9)
- Owen McGivern correspondence and clipping, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17: 10)
- Emily C. Stone correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 17: 11)
- Kay Sugahara correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 17: 12)
- George H. W. Bush correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 17: 13)
- Nancy Dewey Hoppin correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 17: 14)
- Martin S. Quigley correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 17: 15)
- John K. Singlaub correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 17: 16)
- William J. vanden Heuvel correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 17)
- Frank G. Wisner correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 17: 18)
- Kenneth N. Hart correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 17: 19)
- Albert E. Jolis, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 17: 20)
- Geoffrey Jones correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 17: 21)
- Robert W. Kearns, 1994 (Box-folder 17: 22)
- Francis L. Kellog correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 23)
- Donor list and correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 18: 1)
- Correspondence relating to George Soros, 1994 (Box-folder 18: 2)
- Donor list, 1998 (Box-folder 18: 3)
- William E. Colby letter to donors, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 4-5)
- Correspondence with donors, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 18: 6)
- Advisory Council letter, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 7)
- Letter to friends of the Foundation, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 8)
- Geoffrey Jones letter to Board of Directors, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 9-10)
- Biographical materials relating to William J. Donovan, 1947-1999 (Box-folder 18: 11)
- Photographs and portrait depicting William J. Donovan, 1918-1991 (Box-folder 18: 12)
- Clippings relating to philanthropy, undated (Box-folder 19: 1-2)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 3)
- Announcement and letter relating to Donovan Fellowships, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and newsletter relating to philanthropy, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 19: 5)
- Budgets, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 6)
- Clippings and printed matter relating to fundraising, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 19: 7-8)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1998 (Box-folder 19: 9)
- Framed portrait of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 20: 1)
- Framed photographs depicting award ceremonies, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 20: 2-6)
- Framed photographs depicting award ceremonies, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 21: 1-6)
- Framed photographs depicting award ceremonies, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 22: 1-7)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 8)
- Special Forces Club correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 23: 1-2)
- Special Forces Club minutes of meetings, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 23: 3)
- Special Forces Club membership applications, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 23: 4)
- Veterans of OSS correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 23: 5)
- Special Forces Club newsletters, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 24: 1)
- Special Forces Club correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 24: 2-4)
- Articles and clippings relating to proposed National Historical Intelligence Museum, 1960-1984 (Box-folder 24: 5)
- Budget, 1982 (Box-folder 24: 6)
- Clippings relating to fundraising, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 24: 7)
- Fundraising correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 8)
- Fundraising position paper, 1982 (Box-folder 24: 9)
- Outline of proposal draft, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 10)
- Proposal for Sarah Scaife Foundation, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 11)
- Correspondence and list relating to contributors, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 24: 12-14)
- Letters to the editor, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 24: 15)
- Donovan Award dinner correspondence and bills, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 16)
- Bryan-Elliott Co., correspondence relating to museum display, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 17)
- National Historical Intelligence Museum correspondence, undated (Box-folder 24: 18)
- Memorandum to Directors relating to educational programs, undated (Box-folder 24: 19)
- Aide-mémoire, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 1)
- Foundation brochure drafts, printed copy, bills, and correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 2-7)
- Other brochures and newsletters, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 8)
- Membership list, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 9)
- Correspondence relating to Donovan medal and scroll, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 10)
- Correspondence relating to design of envelope and memorandum, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 11)
- List of donors, 1984 (Box-folder 25: 12)
- Jaydan Press correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 13)
- Invoices for secretarial services, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 14)
- Correspondence relating to Donovan dinner, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 15)
- Administrative file, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 16)
- Tiffany & Co. correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 25: 17)
- List of potential donors, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 18)
- Correspondence and clippings relating to potential contributors, undated (Box-folder 25: 19)
- Letters to Board of Directors and Advisory Council, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 1)
- Mailing to membership, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 2)
- Frank Wisner correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 3-4)
- List of funds received, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 5)
- Biographical materials relating to William J. Donovan, 1959-1981 (Box-folder 26: 6)
- Initial program proposal, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 7)
- Position papers, 1982 (Box-folder 26: 8)
- Originals of by-laws, minutes of meetings, and proposals, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 26: 9)
- Early Foundation papers, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 26: 10)
- Articles on intelligence services and espionage, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 26: 11)
- Invoices, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 26: 12-13)
- Fundraising appeal, 1998 (Box-folder 27: 1)
- Jonathan E. Colby correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 27: 2)
- Letters to Directors, 1997 (Box-folder 27: 3-5)
- William J. vanden Heuvel correspondence and writing on William J. Donovan, 1958-1996 (Box-folder 27: 6)
- Walter J. P. Curley correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 7)
- Lists of possible members of Advisory Council, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 27: 8)
- Joseph Verner Reed correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 27: 9)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 27: 10)
- Francis L. Kellogg correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 27: 11)
- John R. Drexel IV correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27: 12)
- List of office fund contributions, 1999 (Box-folder 27: 13)
- Lists of donors, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 27: 14-15)
- Portrait of William J. Donovan, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 28: 1-3)
- Letter from Albert E. Jolis to Directors, 1994 (Box-folder 28: 4)
- Donovan Fellowship Program correspondence and invoices, 1994 (Box-folder 28: 5)
- William J. Colby letter to membership, 1994 (Box-folder 28: 6)
- Frank G. Wisner letter to George W. Bush, 1998 (Box-folder 28: 7)
- Listed of assisted activities, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 28: 8)
- Financial correspondence and list of donors, 1994 (Box-folder 28: 9)
- Appeal to donors, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 10)
- Ruth C. Reardon correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 28: 11)
- Letters from Albert E. Jolis to Directors, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 28: 12-13)
- Albert E. Jolis biographical materials, undated (Box-folder 28: 14)
- List of donors, 1996 (Box-folder 28: 15)
- Letter promoting William J. Donovan poster and statuette, 1996 (Box-folder 29: 1)
- List of Donovan Award winners, 1996 (Box-folder 29: 2)
- Appeal to donors, 1994 (Box-folder 29: 3)
- William Stephenson correspondence, 1986 (Box-folder 29: 4)
- Miscellaneous clippings and newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 29: 5)
- Ledger sheets, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 29: 6)
- Monographs relating to charity and the Fulbright program, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 29: 7-8)
- Record of deposits, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 30: 1-2)
- Donovan statuette correspondence, undated (Box-folder 30: 3-4)
- Donovan portrait correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 30: 5)
- Copies of deposit slips, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 30: 6)
- Charter patron certificate, 1984 (Box-folder 30: 7)
- Donovan statuette, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 30: 8-14)
- Framed portraits of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 31: 1-4)
- Summary of meeting with Frank R. Barnett, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 1)
- Letter from George A. Birrell, 1984 (Box-folder 32: 2)
- Richard Dunlop correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 32: 3)
- Letter to Pierre Fourcaud, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 4)
- Lawrence R. Houston correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 32: 5)
- Memorandum to Ann Willets Boyd, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 6)
- John Weitz correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 32: 7)
- Letter about Frances G. Scaife contribution, 1999 (Box-folder 32: 8)
- Letter from Charles W. Hostler, 1999 (Box-folder 32: 9)
- David R. Jewell correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 32: 10)
- Julian M. Niemczyk correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 32: 11)
- Claiborne Pell, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 32: 12)
- Address register of Advisory Council, 1999 (Box-folder 32: 13)
- Harold Baker correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 32: 14)
- A. Vernon Carnahan correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 15)
- Letter to Barbara H. Colby, 1998 (Box-folder 32: 16)
- Patrick Sean Dolan, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 32: 17)
- Letter to Leona Forman, 1998 (Box-folder 32: 18)
- Acceptance letters, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 19)
- Resignation and refusal letters, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 20)
- Invitations to join Advisory Council, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 21-22)
- Lists of advisers, undated (Box-folder 32: 23-24)
- Advisory Council fundraising records, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 25)
- List of non-contributors, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 26)
- Paid bills and invoices, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 33: 1-2)
- Tax returns, 1997 (Box-folder 33: 3)
- General file, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 4)
- Correspondence with Directors, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 33: 5)
- Non-member correspondence, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 33: 6-10)
- Advisory Council correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 33: 11)
- Letter from John J. McLoy, 1984 (Box-folder 33: 12)
- Letter from William J. Morgan, 1986 (Box-folder 33: 13)
- Paid bills and invoices, 1994 (Box-folder 34: 1)
- Account statements, 1994 (Box-folder 34: 2)
- Tax returns, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 34: 3)
- Reunion financial records, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 4)
- Tax correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 34: 5)
- Tax forms, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 34: 6)
- Award dinner correspondence and financial records, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 7)
- Chicago reunion correspondence and financial records, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 8)
- Donovan Award dinner financial records, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 9)
- Paid bills and invoices, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 10)
- Miscellaneous financial records, 1995 (Box-folder 35: 1)
- Paid bills and invoices, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 35: 2-3)
- Record of contributions, 1996 (Box-folder 35: 4)